[
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_Primrose_00",
		"AchievementId": "13A_SQ_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_04 || 99_MSQ_34",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_Primrose_01",
		"AchievementId": "13A_SQ_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "13A_SQ_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_Primrose_01",
		"AchievementId": "13A_SQ_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "13A_SQ_02",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_14_GetTorches",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_Pyro_00",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_17",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_04 || 99_MSQ_34",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_Pyro_01",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_18",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_17",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_Pyro_01",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_19",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_18",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_MonsterHunter_01",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_20",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_11 || 99_MSQ_34",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_05_FindHunters",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_MonsterHunter_02",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_21",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_20",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_MonsterHunter_03",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_23",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_21",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_17_KillGators",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_17_KillGators_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_AnimalHunter_01",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_24",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_04 || 99_MSQ_34",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_17_KillGators_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_17_KillGators_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_17_KillGators_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_17_KillGators_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_17_KillGators_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_17_KillGators_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_17_KillGators_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_18_KillBoar",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_AnimalHunter_02",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_25",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_24",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CoatingBeastT4",
		"ItemRewardQty": 3,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_AnimalHunter_03",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_26",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_25",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_AnimalHunter_03",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_27",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_26",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_Architect_01",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_28",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_11 || 99_MSQ_34",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_Architect_02",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_29",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_28",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_Architect_03",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_30",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_29",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_PerfumeAlchemist",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_31",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_11 || 99_MSQ_34",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_Antiquarian_01",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_32",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_02 || 99_MSQ_34",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_Antiquarian_02",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_33",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_32",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_AntiquarianSpouse_00",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_34",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_33",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "13A_Antiquarian_03",
		"AchievementId": "13_Quest_35",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_34",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_28_BearUrine",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"Task": "13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "9904_MSQ_Theophrastus",
		"AchievementId": "99_MSQ_28",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_05 || 99_MSQ_27",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Title": "@13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_objective_title",
		"Description": "@13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	}
]